sony-mea.com 2006-06-16

# Sony Middle East and Africa

**Personal Information Management Policy**  
Sony Gulf FZE - Privacy Notice 

Sony Gulf FZE knows that you care about how information about you is used and shared and appreciates the trust you have placed in the company. This notice describes our privacy policy. By submitting information about yourself, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy notice.

For each visitor to a Sony Gulf website, Sony Gulf's web server automatically recognizes and stores information, such as the visitor's IP address/domain name combination and any referring websites. We use this information to understand visitor traffic patterns through our websites for purposes such as enhancing their usability. Your computer provides this information automatically each time you log on, unless you've activated blocking technology available in some browsers. Additionally, Sony Gulf may ask you to provide "personal information" --- meaning, individually identifiable information such as your e-mail address, name, mailing address, or telephone number, which can be associated with individually identifiable information, to enable you to participate in contests, fill out a registration, or answer a survey. 

Sony Gulf may combine the information you provide on our websites with other information we may collect from you offline or from third parties so that we can more effectively tailor our website, services, and offerings to you. Sony Gulf FZE may share the information with the various departments in our company and /or any affiliated companies of Sony Corporation, more than 50% of whose outstanding stocks or interests with voting rights are directly or indirectly owned by Sony Corporation. The information may also be shared with our distributors and advertising agencies. Transfer of information will only be done to those companies, with whom Sony Gulf has an agreement that controls usage of information in a manner similar to the conditions mentioned in this privacy notice. Sony Gulf will be obliged to release personal information, when required by law. No other disclosure of your information will be made without your prior consent. If you provide Sony Gulf with personal information, you shall have the right, on reasonable prior notice, to inspect, change, amend, or delete such information. Instructions on how to update personal information will be given at the point of data collection. No other use of the information will be made without your prior consent.

**If you are under 13 years of age, you may submit your personal details only with involvement of a parent or guardian.**

If you would like to review, update, modify or delete your personal information; limit or revoke any consent previously given or stop receiving any communication from Sony Gulf FZE, please inform us by sending an e-mail to [webmaster@ap.sony.com](mailto:webmaster@ap.sony.com).

Sony Gulf FZE will delete in a non-reproducible manner any personal information that is no longer necessary or upon a deletion advise from you.
